 var JsonStrEng= '{"Exam":{"Questions":[{"QuestionBody":"The major language of World Wide Web is HTML.","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"2","Answers":[" true "," false"],"CorrectAnswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":"HTML is an abbreviation for...HiTech Markup Language","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"2","Answers":[" true "," false"],"CorrectAnswer":"2"},{"QuestionBody":"Transmitter is a device from where the information is sent.","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"2","Answers":[" true "," false"],"CorrectAnswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":"LAN is an abbreviation for?.","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" Large Access Network"," Local Access Network"," Large Area Network"," Local Area Network"],"CorrectAnswer":"4"},{"QuestionBody":"URL is an abbreviation for?.","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" Universal Resource Locator"," Uniform Resource Locator"," Universal Resource Location"," Uniform Resource Location"],"CorrectAnswer":"4"},{"QuestionBody":"FTP is an abbreviation for?.","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" File Transfer Position"," File Transfer Protection"," File Transfer Protocol"," File Transfer Possibility"],"CorrectAnswer":"3"},{"QuestionBody":"IDE stands for?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" Integrated Dual Environment"," Inter Development Environment"," Integrated Development Environment"," Inter Dual Environment"],"CorrectAnswer":"3"},{"QuestionBody":"Dairy farming is at leading agricultural activity in the United States","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"2","Answers":[" true "," false"],"CorrectAnswer":"2"},{"QuestionBody":"The dawn redwood appears to have flourished some 100 million years ago in northern forests around the world.","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"2","Answers":[" true "," false"],"CorrectAnswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":" Two species of large mammals once dominated the North American Prairies: the American bison and the pronghorn antelope..","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"2","Answers":[" true "," false"],"CorrectAnswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":"Tom has me English lesson on Thursdays.","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"2","Answers":[" true "," false"],"CorrectAnswer":"2"},{"QuestionBody":"This film is better than his last one.","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"2","Answers":[" true "," false"],"CorrectAnswer":"2"},{"QuestionBody":"I am a teacher. ____________ do you do? - Nice to meet you!","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-How","b-What","c-who","d-where"],"CorrectAnswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":"I am fair ____________ my sister is dark.","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-but","b-because","c-that","d-so"],"CorrectAnswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":"I am hungry! Is there ____________ fruit in the cupboard?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-some","b-alot","c-any","d-much"],"CorrectAnswer":"3"},{"QuestionBody":"I ____________ go to the seaside at the weekend.","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-often","b-like much","c-many","d-more"],"CorrectAnswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":"Amanda can ____________ all night long!","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-dancing","b-to dance","c-dance","d-is dance"],"CorrectAnswer":"3"},{"QuestionBody":"It is the telephone box _________ the market.","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-in front of","b-in front","c-on the front","d-front"],"CorrectAnswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":"________ girls over there are English.","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-that","b-these","c-those","d-this"],"CorrectAnswer":"3"},{"QuestionBody":"He sleeps during the day and works ___ night.","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-at","b-at the","c-on the","d-in the"],"CorrectAnswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":"_______ painting over there is beautiful.","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-that","b-these","c-those","d-this"],"CorrectAnswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":"She works hard during the day and sleeps well ______ night.","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-at","b-at the","c-in the","d-the"],"CorrectAnswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":"The cheese is ____________ the eggs in the fridge.","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-behind","b-in front","c-in","d-above"],"CorrectAnswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":"They can ____________ chess very well.","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-play","b-to play","c-playing","d-is play"],"CorrectAnswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":"I ____________ go jogging on the beach at the weekend.","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-a lot of","b-much","c-sometimes","d-many"],"CorrectAnswer":"3"},{"QuestionBody":" I would like ____________ fruit, please.","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-a lot","b-any","c-some","d-many"],"CorrectAnswer":"3"},{"QuestionBody":"I am fat ____________ Tim is thin.","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-and","b-or","c-but","d-so"],"CorrectAnswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":"She is fine. And ____________ is your wife?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-who","b-what","c-how","d-where"],"CorrectAnswer":"3"},{"QuestionBody":"Tom is a ____________ football player than Peter.","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-bad","b-worse","c-worst","d-badder"],"CorrectAnswer":"2"},{"QuestionBody":"I play games on ____________ computer in the evenings.","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-you","b-hers","c-my","d-your"],"CorrectAnswer":"3"}]}}';
       
 var JsonStrIQ='{"Exam":{"Questions":[{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 2, 4, 6, 8, 10, ...What numbershould come next?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 11"," 12"," 13"," 14"],"CorrectAnswer":"2"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 58, 52, 46, 40, 34,...What number should come next?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 26"," 28"," 30","28"],"CorrectAnswer":"2"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 40, 40, 47, 47, 54,...Whatnumber should come next?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 40"," 44"," 54"," 61"],"CorrectAnswer":"3"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 544, 509, 474, 439,...What number should come next?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["404"," 414","420","445"],"CorrectAnswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 201, 202, 204, 207,...What number should come next?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 205"," 208"," 210"," 211"],"CorrectAnswer":"4"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 8, 22, 8, 28, 8, ...What number should come next?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 9"," 29"," 32"," 34"],"CorrectAnswer":"4"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 80, 10, 70, 15, 60,...What number should come next?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 20"," 25"," 30"," 50"],"CorrectAnswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 36, 34, 30, 28, 24,...Whatnumber should come next?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 20","22"," 23"," 26"],"CorrectAnswer":"2"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 22, 21, 23, 22, 24, 23 What number should come next?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 22"," 24"," 25"," 26"],"CorrectAnswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 3, 4, 7, 8, 11, 12,...What number should come next?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 7"," 10"," 14"," 15"],"CorrectAnswer":"4"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 31, 29, 24, 22, 17, ...What number should come next?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 15","14","13","12"],"CorrectAnswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 21, 9, 21, 11, 21, 13,...What number should come next?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 14"," 15"," 21"," 23"],"CorrectAnswer":"3"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 7, 10, 8, 11, 9, 12, ...What number should come next?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 7","10"," 12"," 13"],"CorrectAnswer":"2"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 14, 28, 20, 40, 32, 64,...What number should come next?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 52"," 56"," 96"," 128"],"CorrectAnswer":"2"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 1,000, 200, 40,...What number should come next?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 8"," 10"," 15"," 20"],"CorrectAnswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 1.5, 2.3, 3.1, 3.9,...What number should come next?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 4.2"," 4.4"," 4.7"," 5.1"],"CorrectAnswer":"3"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 5.2, 4.8, 4.4, 4,...What number should come next?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 3"," 3.3"," 3.5"," 3.6"],"CorrectAnswer":"4"},{"QuestionBody":"84 78 72 66 60 54 48","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["44 34"," 42 36"," 42 32"," 40 34"],"CorrectAnswer":"2"},{"QuestionBody":"3 8 13 18 23 28 33","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 39 44"," 38 44"," 38 43"," 37 42"],"CorrectAnswer":"3"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 8, 43, 11, 41, __, 39, 17,...What number should ?ll in the blank?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 8"," 14"," 43"," 44"],"CorrectAnswer":"2"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 15, __, 27, 27, 39, 39,...What number should ?ll the blank?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 51"," 39"," 23"," 15"],"CorrectAnswer":"4"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 83, 73, 93, 63, __, 93, 43, . . What number should ?ll the blank?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 33"," 53"," 73"," 93"],"CorrectAnswer":"2"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 4, 7, 25, 10, __, 20, 16, 19,...What number should ?ll the blank?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 13"," 15"," 20"," 28"],"CorrectAnswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 72, 76, 73, 77, 74, __, 75,...What number should ?ll the blank?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 70"," 71","75"," 78"],"CorrectAnswer":"4"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 70, 71, 76, __, 81, 86, 70, 91,...What number should ?ll the blank?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 70"," 71"," 80"," 96"],"CorrectAnswer":"3"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 664, 332, 340, 170, __, 89,...What number should ?ll the blank?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 85"," 97"," 109"," 178"],"CorrectAnswer":"4"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: 0.15, 0.3, __, 1.2, 2.4, . . .What number should ?ll the blank?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" 4.8"," 0.006"," 0.6"," 0.9"],"CorrectAnswer":"3"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: U32, V29, __, X23, Y20, . . .What number should ?ll the blank?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" W26"," W17"," Z17"," Z26"],"CorrectAnswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: F2, __, D8, C16, B32, . . .What number should ?ll the blank?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" A16"," G4"," E4"," E3"],"CorrectAnswer":"3"},{"QuestionBody":"Look at this series: J14, L16, __, P20, R22, . . .What number should ?ll the blank?","QuestionDegree":"10","QuestionType":"1","Answers":[" S24"," N18"," M18"," T24"],"CorrectAnswer":"2"},{"QuestionBody":" Which one of the five is least like the other four?","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-Dog","b-Mouse","c-Lion","d-Snake"],"correctanswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":" Which number should come next in the series? 1 - 1 - 2 - 3 - 5 - 8 - 13","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-8","b-13","c-21","d-26"],"correctanswer":"3"},{"QuestionBody":" Which one of the five choices makes the best comparison? PEACH is to HCAEP as 46251 is to:","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-15264","b-23456","c-56323","d-12345"],"correctanswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":" Mary, who is sixteen years old, is four times as old as her brother. How old will Mary be when she is twice as old as her brother?","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-20","b-24","c-25","d-22"],"correctanswer":"2"},{"QuestionBody":" Which one of the numbers does not belong in the following series?2 - 3 - 6 - 7 - 8 - 14 - 15 - 30","Answers":["a-3","b-8","c-15","d-14"],"correctanswer":"2"},{"QuestionBody":" Which one of the five choices makes the best comparison? Finger is to Hand as Leaf is to:","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-Twig","b-Tree","c-Branch","d-Bark"],"correctanswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":" Choose the number that is 1/4 of 1/2 of 1/5 of 200:","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-5","b-20","c-4","d-15"],"correctanswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":" If you rearrange the letters ( CIFAIPC ) you would have the name of a(n):","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-River","b-Animal","c-Ocean","d-City"],"correctanswer":"3"},{"QuestionBody":" John needs 13 bottles of water from the store. John can only carry 3 at a time. What is the minimum number of trips John needs to make to the store?","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-3","b-5","c-4","d-2"],"correctanswer":"2"},{"QuestionBody":" choose the word most similar to Trustworthy:","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-Reliable","b-Relevant","c-Resolute","d-Insolent"],"correctanswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":" If you rearrange the letters ( LNGEDNA ) you have the name of a(n):","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-Country","b-state","c-City","d-Ocean"],"correctanswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":" Which one of the numbers does not belong in the following series? 1 - 2 - 5 - 10 - 13 - 26 - 29 - 48","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-1","b-5","c-48","d-40"],"correctanswer":"3"},{"QuestionBody":" Ralph likes 25 but not 24; he likes 400 but not 300; he likes 144 but not 145. Which does he like:","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-10","b-50","c-1600","d-40"],"correctanswer":"3"},{"QuestionBody":" What is the missing number in the sequence shown below?  1 - 8 - 27 - ? - 125 - 216","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-64","b-10","c-100","d-4"],"correctanswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":" Which one of the following things is the least like the others?","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-Flower","b-Novel","c-State","d-paint"],"correctanswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":" What number should replace the question mark( 0, 4, 2, 6, 3, 7, 3.5, ? )","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-7.5","b-4","c-7","d-9"],"correctanswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":" Please enter the missing number:( 4, 8, 14, 22, ?)","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-28","b-32","c-11","d-10"],"correctanswer":"4"},{"QuestionBody":" One word in this list does not belong to the same group: Pound, Franc, Penny, Mark.","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-Mark","b-Pound","c-Franc","d-Penny"],"correctanswer":"2"},{"QuestionBody":" There are 12 pens on the table, you took 3, how many do you have?","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-7","b-6","c-0","d-3"],"correctanswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":" What is the number that is one half of one quarter of one tenth of 480?","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-24","b-16","c-6","d-12"],"correctanswer":"4"},{"QuestionBody":" Which number should come next in this series(25,24,22,19,15) ? ","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-20","b-10","c-60","d-12"],"correctanswer":"2"},{"QuestionBody":" At a conference, 12 members shook hands with each other before & after the meeting. How many total number of hand shakes occurred? ","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-132","b-100","c-212","d-124"],"correctanswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":" The day after the day after tomorrow is four days before Monday. What day is it today? ","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-Monday","b-Friday","c-Wednesday","d-Tuesday"],"correctanswer":"1"},{"QuestionBody":" 6121135 is to flame as 21215120 is to ?","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-castle","b-bald","c-voice","d-bloat"],"correctanswer":"4"},{"QuestionBody":" Forest is to tree as tree is to ?","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-plant","b-mangrove","c-leaf","d-branch"],"correctanswer":"3"},{"QuestionBody":" Rearrange the following letters to make a word and choose the category in which it fits (RAPETEKA) ?","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-city","b-bird","c-fruit","d-vegetable"],"correctanswer":"2"},{"QuestionBody":"  Which number should come next in this series 10, 17, 26, 37, ? ","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-56","b-50","c-52","d-48"],"correctanswer":"2"},{"QuestionBody":" Rearrange the following letters to make a word and choose the category in which it fits (FADLOFDI) ","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-city","b-bird","c-flower","d-vegetable"],"correctanswer":"3"},{"QuestionBody":" Find the answer that best completes the analogy ( FRUGAL : MISERLY :: RASH :  ? )","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-arrogant","b-profligate","c-spendthrift","d-foolhardy"],"correctanswer":"4"},{"QuestionBody":" Which one of the sets of letters below can be arranged into a five letter English word.","QuestionDegree":"5","QuestionType":"1","Answers":["a-a t r u n","b-p o d e b","c-t e c a r","d-m o h a t"],"correctanswer":"3"}]}}';
       
